long time no see.
久しぶり
It's been a while.
久しぶりです
It's kind of cute again.
またなんか可愛くなったね
thank you.
ありがとうございます
The atmosphere is quite different today.
今日はなんかだいぶ雰囲気が違うんですけど
yes.
はい
Well, just let your hair down normally.
まあなんか普通に髪を下ろしてね
I had it on my headband.
カチューシャにつけてた
I wore it on my headband.
カチューシャにつけてました
What is it today?
今日は何ですか?
Twin tails?
ツインテール?
It's a twin tail.
ツインテールです
It suits you.
似合うね
thank you.
ありがとうございます
Her clothes looked a little sexy last time,
服装も前回なんかちょっとセクシーな感じだったんですけど、
Things are a little off today, girly.
今日はなんかちょっとね、 ガーリー
It has a girly feel to it.
ガ ー リ ーな感じなんですね
That's good.
いい ですね
It looks good with anything.
なんか何でも似合うね
thank you.
ありがとうございます
So, what do you think?
で、どうですか?
I think you and I had a little sex video last time.
前回ちょっと僕とね、 ハメ撮りをしたと思うんですけども
What do you think?
どうですか?
Looking back now, how did it feel?
今振り返ってどうでした?
What was the experience like?
経験というか、 どんな感じでした?
I was surprised at how quickly it happened.
あっという間でびっくりしました
It felt like it was over in an instant.
一瞬で終わった感じでした
I see.
なるほどね
So, I just wanted to hear from you today.
で、ちょっと今日の連絡をね、 いただいてという感じで、
I've been waiting for the camera for a while today too.
今日もちょっとカメラ待っちゃってるんですけど、
I'd like you to take pictures of various places.
ちょっといろんなところをね、 撮影させてほしいと思ってる
Yes, but today it's not me,
んです が、 今日ちょっと僕じゃなくて、
Actor,
男優さん、
Are there any more?
あと あります?
He's like a so-called AV actor.
そういう、 いわゆるAV男優みたいな
No.
ないです
Are you interested in something?
なんか興味あってしますか?
I'll be working with that kind of actor.
そういう男優さんとやる
yes.
はい
Well, today I'll be playing with an actor.
じゃあちょっと今日は、 男優さんとのプレイという感じにね、
I'm going to take some photos, but...
僕 がちょっと撮影させてもらうんですけど、
What do you think?
どうですか?
My current state of mind.
今の心境というか
yes.
はい
What does it feel like?
どんな感じでしょうか?
I'm excited.
ワクワクします
Are you excited?
ワクワクしますか?
I'm looking forward to it.
楽しみです
Hey, it's me and that.
ちょっとあれね、僕とあれなんで、
Can I read it right away?
早速も読んじゃってもいいですか?
thank you.
よろしくお願いします
please.
お願いします
I was looking at it there, and it was all sore,
そこで見てたけど、 しこっちゃってましたけど、
It's cute.
かわいいですね
thank you.
ありがとうございます
I want to get into it right away.
すぐにでもぶち込みたいですよ、僕は
You're naughty.
あなたエッチだね
Isn't that true?
そんなことないの?
yes.
はい
I've only seen him sitting so far,
まだ座ってるところしか見てないんで、
yes.
はい
Can I take a picture just once?
ちょっと 一回撮ってもいいですか?
Same kill.
同じキルだね
It's on.
つ いてる
Your skin is beautiful.
肌きれいだね
If you cover up the soot, you can see her panties.
すすを隠し上げたら、 そのパンティー見えちゃうやつ
That's enough, once you hide the soot.
十分です、すすを隠し上げたら
Don't make yourself look embarrassed.
恥ずかしい格好をさせない
What can I do to make my nipples feel good?
乳首どうすると気持ちいいんだっけ?
Is that so?
そうなの?
This feels good enough though.
十分、これ気持ちよさそうだけど
Wow, those nipples are so big.
すごい、乳首ビンビンじゃん
Don't touch it.
触れぬいじゃん
Do you want to be undressed?
脱がされたい?
There must be a nice hole.
綺麗な穴あるだろうね
yes.
はい
Kneel.
膝立ち
Is it easy to feel?
感じやすいの?
That's amazing.
すごいね
It feels a little tight.
ちょっと締めてる感じするわけや
It's a little slimy.
ちょっとぬるっとしてる
Easy to get wet.
ぬるやすい
It's so beautiful.
すっごい綺麗じゃん
It's amazing, it's deep inside.
すごいね、奥トロトロだね
Does it feel good?
気持ちいいの?
気持ちいい?
I wanted it to be stronger.
もっと強く、欲しかったね
intense.
激しい
Is it intense?
激しいの?
Do you like it?
好きなの?
That often?
そんなによく?
Look at the sofa
見てよ、ソファ
ー.
ー
Even if it's like this, it feels good.
こんな かしらでも気持ちいいんだ
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
Do you want me to look behind you?
後ろを見てほしい?
Does it feel good?
気持ちいいの?
Su!
す っ
It's so wet.
ご いグッチョグチョ
Talk?
しゃべる?
I'll show you more.
もっといっぱい見えてやる
He said he could see something.
なんかが見えてたって
I've got my hands on that.
そこ手ついてて
Does it feel good?
気持ちいいの?
Feels good.
気 持 ちいい
Shall we sit down more?
もっと座ろうか
Don't stop even if you go.
行っても止めないでほか
amazing
すごい
hey.
ね
Look, that hand is there.
ほ ら、そこの手は
Isn't it shaped like a chimp?
チンプの形になってるんじゃない?
too
も
You want it, right?
っと 欲しいでしょ
I want more.
もっと欲しいよね
nice.
いいね
Tap in front.
前にペタっと
Just put it on like this.
こうやってペタっと乗せて
Raise your hair.
毛先上げて
Does it feel good?
気持ちいいの?
Now, let's look at it from the other side.
ほら、今度反対側に見てみようか
Push it out really hard.
すごい押し出して
That's amazing.
すごいね
I'll push it out.
押し出すね
Does it feel good?
気持ちいいの?
It feels good.
気持ちいいね
Can I take it out inside?
中で出していい?
I'm so excited.
ドクドクしてるね
Do you see that it's hanging all the way down to your butt?
お尻までたれてるの分かる?
minutes
分か
Ru.
る
I can say that.
そう いうことできるんだ
You didn't do that much for me?
俺の時そんなにしてくれなかったの?
I don't remember.
覚えてないです
I forgot.
忘れちゃいました
It went by so quickly that I was surprised at how good it felt.
あっという間すぎて、気持ちよさとびっくりでした